question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Books",
     "question": "The Harry Potter series of books, combined, are over 1,000,000 words in length.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "In 1993, Prince changed his name to an unpronounceable symbol because he was unhappy with his "
                 "contract with Warner Bros.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "The 2010 film 'The Social Network' is a biographical drama film about MySpace founder Tom "
                 "Anderson.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Geography",
     "question": "Alaska is the largest state in the United States.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Politics",
                                       "question": "Former president Theodore Roosevelt (1900-1908)  ran for another "
                                                   "term under the Progressive Party in 1912.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Animals",
     "question": "The Axolotl is an amphibian that can spend its whole life in a larval state.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Peter Molyneux was the founder of Bullfrog Productions.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
     "question": "&quot;PAYDAY: The Heist&quot; is a sequel to the board game &quot;Payday&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The name of the main character of the video game &quot;The Legend of Zelda&quot;, is Zelda.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Mythology",
     "question": "In Norse mythology, Thor once dressed as a woman.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
